[
  {
    "id_2": "p1",
    "sentence": "The children ran outside to",
    "word": "play",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "The children did not play.",
    "correct_response": "n",
    "left_or_right": "right",
    "trigger_value": 8
  },
  {
    "id_2": "p2",
    "sentence": "On Valentine’s Day the woman received a single red",
    "word": "rose",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "The woman got a lot of gifts on Valentine's Day.",
    "correct_response": "n",
    "left_or_right": "left",
    "trigger_value": 7
  },
  {
    "id_2": "p3",
    "sentence": "The princess would someday become a",
    "word": "queen",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "The princess would become a queen in the future.",
    "correct_response": "y",
    "left_or_right": "left",
    "trigger_value": 7
  },
  {
    "id_2": "p4",
    "sentence": "The Parkers’ baby could already say three",
    "word": "words",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "The Parker's baby can say some words.",
    "correct_response": "y",
    "left_or_right": "left",
    "trigger_value": 7
  },
  {
    "id_2": "p5",
    "sentence": "The grandmother left everything to her son in her",
    "word": "will",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "The grandmother left nothing to her son.",
    "correct_response": "n",
    "left_or_right": "right",
    "trigger_value": 8
  },
  {
    "id_2": "p6",
    "sentence": "The fluffy white clouds are high up in the",
    "word": "sky",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "There are fluffy white clouds in the sky.",
    "correct_response": "y",
    "left_or_right": "left",
    "trigger_value": 7
  },
  {
    "id_2": "p7",
    "sentence": "To promote their album the band went on",
    "word": "tour",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "The band promote their album with a tour.",
    "correct_response": "y",
    "left_or_right": "right",
    "trigger_value": 8
  },
  {
    "id_2": "p8",
    "sentence": "Katie put the flowers in an expensive",
    "word": "vase",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "Katie stored the flowers in a cheap vase.",
    "correct_response": "n",
    "left_or_right": "right",
    "trigger_value": 8
  },
  {
    "id_2": "p9",
    "sentence": "The maid dusted the books on the",
    "word": "shelf",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "The maid cleaned the books on the shelf.",
    "correct_response": "y",
    "left_or_right": "left",
    "trigger_value": 7
  },
  {
    "id_2": "p10",
    "sentence": "The birthday card was funny and made me",
    "word": "laugh",
    "sentence_type": "practice",
    "question": "I did not enjoy the birthday card.",
    "correct_response": "n",
    "left_or_right": "right",
    "trigger_value": 8
  }
]